worldslist.com 2006-11-10

# Worldslist : Terms of Use

  |  **Privacy Policy**

Worldslist has established this privacy policy to explain to you how your information is protected, collected and used, which may be updated by Worldslist from time to time. Worldslist will provide notice of materially significant changes to this privacy policy by posting notice on the Worldslist site. 

**1\. Protecting your privacy**

  * We don't share your information with third parties for marketing purposes. 
  * We don't engage in cross-marketing. 
  * We don't employ tracking devices for marketing purposes ("cookies", "web beacons," single-pixel gifs). 
  * We offer email anonymization & relay, to reduce 3rd party harvesting & spam. 
  * Account information is password-protected. Keep your password safe. 
  * Worldslist does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If worldslist learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 13, Worldslist will remove that posting. 

**2\. Data we collect**

  * We sometimes collect your email address, for purposes such as sending self-publishing and confirmation emails, authenticating user accounts, providing subscription email services, registering for forums, etc.  
  * We may collect personal information if you provide it in feedback or comments, post it on our classifieds or interactive forums, or if you contact us directly. Please do not post any personal information on Worldslist forums or classifieds that you expect to keep private. 
  * Our web logs collect standard web log entries for each page served, including your IP address, page URL and timestamp.    

**3\. Data we store**

  * All classified and forum postings are stored in our database, even after "deletion," and may be archived. 
  * Our web logs and other records are stored as well.  
  * Although we make good faith efforts to store the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security. 

**4\. Archiving and display of worldslist postings by search engines and other sites**

    Search engines and other sites not affiliated with worldslist - including  [google.com](http://www.google.com/), and [yahoo.com](http://groups.yahoo.com/) \- archive or otherwise make available worldslist postings, including resumes 

**5\. Circumstances in which worldslist may release information**

  * Worldslist may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. 
  * Worldslist may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Use; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of worldslist, its users or the general public. 

**6\. International Users**

By visiting our web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of Worldslist we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, please understand that such data may be stored on servers located in the United States. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data. 

**7\. Feedback**   
We welcome your feedback on this document in our feedback forum.
